I hate television.
我讨厌电视
It gives me headaches.
它让我头痛
You know，there's so many magnetic waves traveling in the airspace
太多电磁波在空间里流窜
because of TV and television，
因为电视和电视机
we're losing ten times as many brain cells as we're supposed to.
我们丧失了十倍的脑细胞
Please！
拜托
「The cow says blank.」 Three letters.
牛会呜呜叫
Dude！
笨
「Dude.」 I don't know.
不知道啦
Magnetic waves，brain cells.
电波和脑细胞…
I don't understand the connection between all that stuff.
我不知道其中有何关连
You know what else I heard？
你知道我听说了什么吗
Magnetic waves shrink silicone molecules.
电波会让矽胶愈缩愈小
Oh，my God！Turn it off！
天呀 关掉啦
- It's not working！- It's backwards！
- 遥控失灵了 - 你拿反了
- What do we do？- I don't know！
- 我们怎么办 - 我不知道
Oh，God！
天啊
Thank God。I can't afford to get any smaller.
谢天谢地 变小我可完了
Come on。You're beautiful.
拜托 你多漂亮
I wish I had your legs.
我希望能拥有你的腿
I wish I had your butt.
我希望能拥有你的咪咪
- I wish I had your… - Shaved pussy？
- 我希望能拥有你的… - 白虎苞
Nobody's getting Snowball.
不是每个人都有的
Okay。That thing's kind of scary，anyway.
好啦 好像有点恐怖
- I know something even scarier。- What？
- 我还知道更恐怖的事 - 什么事
Have you heard about this videotape？
你听过录影带的事吗
The one where they do it on the boat？
你是说他们在船上
And then in the car？And then in the bathtub？
然后又车震 又在浴缸里做的那卷
And he's，like，「Hey，baby，I love you.」 And she's，like，「Where are we？」
他说 「宝贝我爱你」 然后她说 「我们在哪里」
- And did you see the… - No。Not that tape.
- 还有… - 不 不是那一卷
The one with all the scary images.
是有恐怖影像的那卷
You know，after you watch the tape，the phone rings，
你看完录影带 电话就响了
and this really scary voice comes on and says you're gonna die in，like…
传出恐怖的声音 说你快死了 就在…
Seven days。Yeah，I saw that one with Josh last weekend.
七天之内 我知道 上星期我和乔许看过了
You were with Josh last weekend？Oh，my God！
你上星期和乔许在一起 天啊
My God！
天啊
Oh，yes，I was.
对呀
You ho！
你这荡妇
You know it！
你明知道的
- This is really weird。- Yeah.
- 真诡异 - 对呀
Big house，only one phone.
这么大的房子 只有一具电话
Hello？
喂
I'm coming for you，my precious.
我来了 宝贝…
- Hi，Mom。- Hi，precious。Having fun？
- 嗨老妈 - 嗨 宝贝 好玩吗
Anyway，we're just about to go to bed.
没啦 正想去睡觉
No。Not like that.
不是 不是那样的
Well，I guess a woman would know how to touch a…
是 我知道的
Hello？
喂
Katie？
凯蒂
Are you okay？
你还好吗
《惊声尖笑3》
God！
天
Tom，did you hear…
汤姆你听见…
The dogs are acting strange.
狗狗怪怪的
Sue！
苏
What are you doing out here？We were worried sick.
你在这里干嘛 我们担心死了
What's wrong？
怎么了
I wonder what they're trying to tell us.
不知道他们想表达什么
And now，Washington，D.C.'s leading morning news program，
现在请收看华盛顿最受欢迎的
the Morning News.
新闻节目
Good morning。I'm Ross Giggins.
早安我是罗斯
For our top story，we turn now to Cindy Campbell.
今天的焦点新闻就交给辛蒂咯
Thank you，Ross.
谢谢你 罗斯
There's a developing story in Middleburg at this hour.
目前在中堡的最新消息
A mysterious crop circle appeared in local farmer，Tom Logan's cornfield.
当地农夫汤姆的玉米田里出现了神秘的麦田圈
Elaborate prank or extraterrestrial phenomenon？
这是人为的恶作剧 还是来自外星的现象
We'll update you as soon as we have any further information，
只要有最新消息 我们将随时插播报道
but，either way，
无论如何
it's clear something strange is happening in that small town。Ross？
小镇上确实发生了奇特事件 罗斯
I'm sorry，I wasn't listening.
报歉我没听到
Coming up，more news after this.
不要转台 我们马上回来
- Cindy，you got a second？- Sure.
- 辛蒂 有空吗 - 有
I want you to take a look at this for that big strip- club expos.
我要你去看看这个重要的脱衣俱乐部
But I'd rather stick with the crop circle story.
我想继续追麦田圈的新闻
Come on。You know those things are just a hoax.
算了 那只是恶作剧罢了
No，I'm telling you，I sense something about that cornfield.
不 听我的 我觉得玉米田里有问题
Call it women's intuition or ESPN or both，
说是女性直觉或是「新店杆」也好
but I can tell when danger's near。I just…
可我觉得危险来了 我只是…
- My eyes！- Cindy，it's sweeps month.
- 我的眼 - 辛蒂 这是结算月了
Ratings mean everything.
收视率决定一切
People want human- interest stories，like the one you did yesterday.
大家喜欢有趣的新闻 像昨天做的那一则
The report on breast augmentation？
隆乳的那一则
It was just ten minutes of topless women.
那只是10分钟的上空女郎
I mean，come on.
我是说拜托
Why are these so interesting？
这有啥有趣的
For God's sake！
拜托好不好
People don't care about this.
人们不在乎这个
They want hard- hitting stories and in- depth coverage and… And…
他们要的是硬里子新闻 有深度的话题 还有…
And twins！
胸部
You think it was the Kreisel boys who cut that stuff into your corn？
你认为是克里森兄弟搞的鬼
All I know is my crops are gone.
我只知道我的玉米毁了
The bank's gonna foreclose if I can't pay the rent.
如果我付不出钱 银行就会没收我的抵押品
I got 60 days to come up with $1.50.
我还有六十天可以筹钱
I'm sorry。The last thing you needed was more…
很遗憾 你不应该再遭遇困境的
…hardship in your life.
尤其是
Especially after what happened to your…
你老婆发生了…
Sheriff，I don't need your sympathy.
警长我不要你的同情
I didn't mean to upset you，Father.
我不是要惹你伤心神父
Please。I'm not a minister anymore.
拜托 我不做神父很久了
I lost my faith that terrible night.
我在那一夜便失去了信仰
Your faith will return，just as sure as the sun will rise.
你一定会重拾信仰的 就像太阳一定从东方升起
Sounds like a long shot.
听来机会不大
Look，there's always an explanation for all this so- called phenomenon.
听着每个现象都有原因
Maybe you're right.
或许你是对的
It was probably just the Kreisels.
可能是克里森兄弟吧
And when I get through with them，
等我跟他们谈过
I doubt you'll be seeing anything strange on this farm for a long time.
你的田里就很久都不会出现怪事了
You'll see.
等着瞧吧
You all right，Tom？Get some rest.
你还好吧 汤姆 休息一下
George！
乔治
I need you back here tomorrow night after you pick up Sue.
明晚你接到苏之后 我要你回这里来
That tractor needs fixing.
那台拖拉机需要修理
Sorry，dawg。I can't help you。I have to get ready for my show.
抱歉老兄 我不能帮你 我得为表演做准备
Not that stupid hip- hop stuff again.
不会又是那愚蠢的嘻哈吧
Damn it，George，when are you gonna do something with your life？
可恶 乔治 你何时才能认真过活
- I got a dream！- What is your dream？
- 我有个梦想 - 什么梦
To have a dream.
就是继续做梦
George，all you've done is chase adolescent fantasies.
乔治 你只是在追寻青少年时期的幻想罢了
「I wanna be an astronaut，a cowboy，gynecologist to the stars.」
你想做太空人 牛仔…名女人的妇产科医师
And now，this stupid hip- hop thing.
现在则想当嘻哈歌手
For your information，this hip-hop thing is gonna get me paid.
让你知道一下哦 唱嘻哈有钱可领
I'm gonna win that rap battle tomorrow night.
明天晚上的饶舌歌比赛我将拔得头筹
Rap battle？For God's sakes.
饶舌歌比赛 天啊
You just hate me 'cause I'm black.
你讨厌我 因为我是黑人
You don't have any faith in me.
你不相信我
You don't have any faith in anything anymore.
你什么都不相信了
So why don't you just worry about you，and I'll worry about…
那你管好自己就够了 我的事我自己…
Cody.
科迪
You're late again，Aunt Cindy.
你又迟到了 辛蒂阿姨
I'm sorry。I was stuck in traffic.
对不起 塞车嘛
- Cindy！- Brenda，hi！
- 辛蒂 - 布兰达嗨
It's great to see you！
见到你真好
- It's been so long。- Too long.
- 好久不见 - 太久了
I've been working so hard.
我工作太忙了
You know，I've had to spend more and more time at the station.
我得花很多时间待在电视台
The news just keeps coming in.
一直有新闻进来
What was the assignment？
功课是什么
Draw your family and friends.
画家人和朋友
So，anyone new in your life，Cindy？
最近有新男人吗
Well，you know，I just haven't found the right guy.
你知道的 没有适合的对象
I'm looking for something more than just good sex.
我要的不只是性
I know，you want commitment.
我知道你需要承诺
No，I want great sex。And when I meet that guy…
不 我要性高潮 当我遇到适合的男人
That's what I'm talking about！
我就说嘛
You want a guy that's gonna hit that thing hard，like…
你需要强强滚的男人
And then flip you over and come at you from the other side.
能跟你翻云覆雨
D- O- double- G.
你知道我在说啥吗
Did I say stop drawing？
我有叫你们停笔吗
And then he'll look at you，like he gonna cut you.
他望着你的样子就好像他想把你砍了
Brenda，you're so romantic.
布兰达你好浪漫啊…
I guess.
可能是吧
Look，when I meet Mr。Right，I'll know.
听着遇到适合的人时我会知道的
Uncle George！
乔治叔叔
Hey，sweetie，come here！
嗨甜心 过来这里
How are you？
你好吗
Go get your stuff，okay？
去拿东西好吗
I know you。You're Tom Logan's brother.
我认识你 你是汤姆的弟弟
- And you're that reporter，Cindy Campbell。- Yeah.
- 你是那个记者 辛蒂 - 对
You did the story on our cop cycles.
你报道我们的麦片圈
Crop circles.
是麦田圈
Right.
对啦
So，you're here to pick up your…
那么 你是来接…
Nephew。Cody.
外甥 科迪
You don't dress like a farmer.
你的穿着不像个农夫
My brother's the farmer.
我哥才是农夫
I'm the rapper.
我是饶舌歌手
For real。And here's the 6- 1- 1 on that.
是真的 来打611查点资讯吧
That's phone repair。You mean 4- 1- 1.
那是障碍台 你要说的是411查号台吧
Right.
对
So，I'll be doing the rap battle at the 23 Club tomorrow night.
明晚我在23俱乐部参加饶舌歌比赛
I don't believe this shit.
我才不相信呢
Word。You two should come down！
我也不信 你们要来啦
I be rappin'，I be cappin'，I be tappin'，I be flappin'，
我会饶舌
I be happening。Ding，bing，wing。Yo！
帽子我戴鸭舌
- Sounds good。- Would，could，should，'hood.
- 唱的真好 - 我会杀蛇
Gug，mug，dug，bug.
乒乒砰砰唷
If we say we'll come，will you shut your ass up？
如果我们答应去 你可以住嘴吗
Okay，then。Fresh。I'll see you guys tomorrow night.
好吧 就酱子 明天晚上见了
- Okay。Bye。- Peace out.
- 好再见 - 拜拜
Now，who the fuck did that？
哪个王八蛋搞的鬼
Honey，what is it？Are you having one of your visions？
亲爱的 怎么了 你又看到那东西了吗
There's a girl with black hair.
有个女孩 黑头发的
She wants to kill you.
她想杀你
Your period starts in three，two，one.
你的月经快来了三…二…一
What else？Cody，what else do you see？
还有什么 科迪 你还见到什么
I see a little boy and a grown woman，but no father.
一个男孩和一个女人 可是没看到爸爸
- Cody。- I see you kneeling in dog shit.
- 科迪 - 我看到你跪在狗屎里
What？
什么
Oh，for God's sake.
老天爷
Cody，don't you understand？
你还不明白吗
As long as we have each other，that's all we need.
只要我们能在一起 这样就够了
Cody，I know things have been tough for you since your mom died.
科迪 我知道你母亲死后 你很不好受
God，I've been so selfish。Always putting my career first.
我真是太自私了 总是以事业为重
From now on，I'm gonna be thinking about you 24…
从现在开始我会整天想着你…
Damn！
可恶
Wait，Cindy！
辛蒂 等等
Honey，I'm gonna be leaving soon，so…
亲爱的 我会离开一阵子 所以…
Do you know who she is？
你认识她吗
No，
不认识
but sometimes she talks to me.
不过她有时候她会跟我说话
She's coming tonight.
今晚她会来
- Father Muldoon！- Cindy.
- 莫顿神父 - 辛蒂
I'm so grateful you could come。I've called all over for babysitters.
很谢谢你过来 我一直打电话找保姆
I don't mind filling in now and then.
偶尔找我没关系
Where is little Cody？
小科迪呢
I don't know。He must be back in his room，playing.
我不知道 他应该在房里在玩吧
Anyway，make sure Cody washes everywhere.
一定要叫他洗澡洗干净
Also，he has a little rash on his behind.
还有他屁股上有个小疹子
Could you rub this lotion on his little bottom？
你可以帮他在小屁屁上擦乳液吗
Just apply it liberally.
只要轻轻擦就可以了
Thank you，Father。Good night.
谢谢你 神父 晚安
Cody.
科迪
Yeah，yeah，yeah。It's getting thick up in here.
是的 是的 今天真是人多多呀
Hey，look，before we get on with the battles tonight，
听着在今晚的比赛开始前
I got a couple announcements to make.
我要做几点宣布
I know y'all are gonna wanna bust a cap in the air for your favorite rapper，
我知道你们都想干掉心中最喜欢的饶舌歌手
but if you could please hold on to your gunfire until the end of the show.
不过 请克制一下想开枪的冲动 等到比赛结束再说
Now，look，let's just put the safeties on.
现在 先把保险关上
It's on the left side of the gun above the trigger guard.
就在扳机的左手边上方
Will somebody get his ass out of here？Get his ass up out of here！
谁把他轰出去好吗 把他赶走
All right。DJ，spin that shit！
好了 DJ 放音乐吧
- My bad。- Mother…
- 我的错 - 去你妈
Brenda，is something wrong？You look scared.
布兰达 怎么了 你看起来吓坏了
I don't know。All that stuff you was saying on TV，
我不知道 你在电视上说的事情…
I just got a weird feeling something bad is heading my way，
我有预感怪事要发生了
like when you see an Asian person behind the wheel of a car.
就像看到女生开车时那种预感
Cindy，after the show，
今晚看完秀
if I don't end up on all fours with some anonymous guy，
如果我没跟陌生人回家
or drink an ass load of Cristal
或喝到脱裤
and have to sleep it off in a dumpster behind the Sizzler，
醉倒在厨房后面的垃圾箱
you think maybe you could come back to my crib and hang out with me？
你可以过来陪我吗
I don't wanna be alone.
我不想独处
Of course I will，Brenda.
当然好 布兰达
I love you！
我爱你
Pay my way，okay？
今天门票算你的哦
Yo，yo，yo，George！What's up with the man with the tightest rapping…
唷 乔治 还好吗 最强的饶舌歌手来也
- What's up，B？What's good？- …on the streets，baby！
- 还好吗 老兄 有啥新鲜事 - 在街上 宝贝
- What's good with you，boy？- Dude！
- 最近有啥新闻 - 哥们！
- What's good，baby？- Dude！
- 有啥新鲜事 - 哥们！
Finally，the white man is gonna school the black man on how to rap.
白人终于要教教黑人如何饶舌啦
- Yeah！- Yeah，I guess.
- 耶 - 耶 是啊
- Word。- How many people are here，you think？
- 说 - 你觉得今天有多少观众
Shit.
狗屎
I don't know，man。100，200 whitey- hating，chrome- packing，
老天我不知耶 一百 两百个带家伙的白人憎恨者
ready to bust a cap in any white boy's ass who ain't bringing that shit.
等着轰掉烂歌手的头
- Yeah。At least。Yeah。- Word.
- 耶 差不多哦 对呀 - 说
What's wrong，George？
那…又怎样呢
You ever wonder when it's time to stop living up here
你有没有想过远离虚幻世界
and start living down here？
回到现实
But what if we stop living over here and move over there？
不如远离这里挪到那里
Shit，my Aunt ShaNeequa used to live over there，man，
我的姑妈曾住在那里
- but that bitch got evicted，though。- Word？
- 不过那三八被赶走了 - 说啥？
- Yeah，I'm dead serious。- What for？
- 是哦 - 为什么
- Mice。- Mice？I thought she had rats.
- 老鼠 - 老鼠 我以为她养了田鼠
No，man。Rats are outside，mice are inside.
田鼠在户外生活 老鼠在家里生活
Yo，but what if a mouse goes outside？Does it become a rat？
那如果老鼠跑到外头去 就变成田鼠罗
And if a rat is in the house，is it a mouse？
如果田鼠待在家里 会变成老鼠吗
I ain't never seen no mouse outside。That's what I'm saying.
我没在外头看过老鼠
That's because it's a rat，fool！
因为它变成田鼠了
Damn。Yeah，you might've just made a fact just now。That's some real shit！
哇靠 你刚陈述了一项事实 真的很深奥
- Fellas，what are you guys talking about？- That's hot！
- 兄弟 在谈些什么 - 太火了
Yo，George，you need something？'Cause I will do anything for you.
乔治 你需要什么吗 什么事我都能帮你
Anything.
任何事情
Well，about those chrome- packing，whitey- hating gangsters，perhaps…
关于那些带家伙又恨白人的兄弟…
- What he need is a hype man。- Word！
- 他需要个宣传 - 说
Yeah，yeah，a- come on.
没错 耶 没错 来吧
You can be his Spliff Star.
你会变成巨星
That's me，that's what I do.
我就是 就是我
That's my job，baby。That's what I do！You know…
那是我的职责
That's what I do。When you a hype man，you take them hits.
只要你会炒作 一定大卖
Now，let's get out there，man！
我们出去吧
Heads or tail，playboy，what's it gonna be？
会是失败还是成功呢
You cannot escape your fate in the streets
你不能逃避你的命运
Okay，I count cash，you count sheep
好吧 我数钞票 你只要躺着干就可以了
You better not sleep on the beats，capisce
你最好振作点
All right，all right，all right！That was hot！
好啦好啦 真是太棒了
That's what I'm talking about。That was hot，right？Right？
这才叫正点 超棒的 对吧 对吧
Yo，what do we think？
唷 你觉得呢
I thought you were both absolutely dreadful.
我觉得你们都很讨厌
- Ghastly。- What？
- 非常讨人厌 - 啥
I don't know what I'm doing here.
我不知道我来干嘛的
This club is totally pathetic.
这里真是太惨了
Everybody put your hands up.
每个人举起手来
This is it。You ready，George？It's show time，baby.
好了 准备好了吗 乔治 上场了 宝贝
- Okay。- I just want to let you know，man，
- 好的 - 我想告诉你 兄弟
that no matter what goes on on that stage tonight，
不论今晚表现如何
you'll always be in my heart.
我心都将与你同在
That's love。That's love right there.
这是真情 真情流漏唷
- I love you。- That's what I'm talking about.
- 我爱你 - 这样就对了
- I love you，man。Can you feel it？- That's what I'm talking about.
- 我爱你 兄弟 能感觉到吗 - 这也是我要说的
- Hey，come here，y'all。Come here。- Can you feel my love on your hip？
- 兄弟 到这儿来 - 你会感觉我的爱
- Can you feel it？- I can't get around！
- 你感觉到吗 - 我无法闪避
- Okay。- Come on，dawg！
- 好 - 来吧 兄弟
- That's what I'm talking about。- You go out there and you rip it tonight.
- 就是这样 - 兄弟 上台去好好来一曲
All right，man？Do your thing tonight，all right？
今晚要大放异彩 好吗
- Okay，cool。All right。- We shouldn't have to do that.
- 我们是兄弟 - 不该互相残杀
- We love each other。- I'm gonna go bring you on.
- 我们彼此友爱 - 我来介绍你出场
Let's do it，baby。We hyped！
上场吧 宝贝 我们罩你
Yeah，all right，all right。Y'all ready for the next throw down？
好了 准备看下一个表演了吗
To my left，we have the reigning champion，
在我左边 是从阿帕契来的
hailing from Fort Apache，the Bronx.
卫冕冠军
BS 1-1-1.
BS 1-1-1
Some of y'all call him 「Jealous Ones Still Envy.」
有人称呼他超级忌妒王
Some of y'all call him the Don Cartagena！
有人称呼他卡塔吉纳先生
Some of y'all call him Joey Crack.
也有人叫他乔伊毁灭者
- Stick 'em up！- But tonight，let's give it up for Fat Joe！
- 投降吧 - 今晚我们为大胖乔鼓掌
I gotta go against him？
我得跟他拼
Give it up！Give it up！
放弃吧 放弃吧
What，you think they're here to see Fat Joe？
你想他们是来看大胖乔的吗
Joe！Joe！Joe！
乔 乔 乔
No，man，they're saying，「Go！Go！Go！」
不 他们在喊 「上 上 上」
Now our challenger.
现在请挑战者上场
He's a farmer rapper，so you know he been kicking the shit all day！
这小子是个农夫 所以他整天在饶舌
Let's give it up for my man，George！
各位观众 请欢迎我兄弟 乔治
That's what I'm talking about！Yeah，yeah！Come on，everybody！
你在说什么话 耶 耶 来吧各位
- That's right。- Put your hands…
- 没错 - 举起手来
That's right。Okay，Joey Crack.
好 乔伊毁灭者
You the reigning champion，so you get to spit first.
你是冠军 所以你先呛声
Yo，DJ，spin that shit！
唷DJ音乐放下去
These guys can't be serious right here.
这家伙不可能成大器
Standing Mini- Me，AKA 「I hope he ain't the one you fight with.」
个头比我小 他怎么跟我比
Hey，yo，this nigga's mad corny And he got no skills
他有玉米一堆 可他无啥小路用
'Cause he's all right But he's not real
虽然他无啥大碍 但也构不成我的灾害
I don't mean to hurt your feelings But you'll never get a deal
我不想伤感情 但你真的没行情
'Cause he's all right But he's not real
因为他成不了气候
You're a needle in the haystack I'm the don，the city slicker
你是大海里的虾米 可是我是鲸鱼
Forget cows and milk your mom's Her titties give ya that elixir
别再管牛和牛奶了 乳臭未干的小孩
Thought he wasn't？
难道你不是吗
Bet this nigga end up Having kids with his cousin
你跟堂妹努力做人算了
Half- retarded My number- one fan be like
还是已经做了 你的一号歌迷
That means Fat Joe's the man！
原来只是唯一
You're a liar in denial
你是王牌的…大骗子
Kill your ass quicker than I died in Empire
打赌你会比我早死
How dare you want to joust with me？
你居然敢跟我挑战
Looking like you dying of SARS Or mad cow disease
我看你还是去医狂牛症比较划算
You fake D- rabbit out to battle me
想要让我回家
Eight miles down the road The farm's that- a- way
八英里外的农场才是你家
Okay。No，no，wait a minute！
好了 非常热闹
All right！All right！That was hot！That was tight，Fat Joe.
非常紧凑的表演大胖乔
Yo！Now，everybody，give it up for my man，George！
唷 各位观众 请欢迎我兄弟 乔治
DJ，spin that shit！
唷DJ音乐催下去
Bitch.
调音
Ho.
贱人
Now everybody in the 2- 0- 2
202区的各位兄弟
Throw your hands in the air 'Cause Fat Joe is through
把你的手举起来 因为大胖乔非常酷
Now everybody in the 2- 0- 2 Throw 'em up
202区的各位兄弟 热起来
Check it out
照过来
I'm a white boy But my neck is red
我是个白人 可我是个硬汉
I put Miracle Whip On my Wonder Bread
我涂美乃滋决不怠慢
My face is pale I've never been in jail
我脸色不好 可我没蹲过苦牢
Me and Buffy spend Every winter in Vail
我和萧蔷每个冬天都到玉山报到
How many bitches have I slapped？Zero
我跟几个女生睡过 没有
And Martha Stewart happens to be my hero
玛莎史都华是我的英雄
I grew up on a farm And I was born with no rhythm
我在农场长大 没有节奏感
Dr。Phil's my uncle And I like to hang with him
菲力医师是我叔叔 我喜欢有他做伴
I can't dance I wear khaki pants
我不会跳舞 我穿卡其裤
My middle name's Lance My grandma's from France
我小名叫阿杜 我奶奶来自法国
So maybe I'm wack 'Cause my skin ain't black
或许我很逊
But you can't talk smack 'Cause whitey just struck back
因为我不够黑
That's what I'm talking about，baby！
但你们不能笑我
- 2-0-2，Fat Joe is through！- 2-0-2，Fat Joe is through！
- 202因为我够酷 - 202因为我够酷
- Give it up for George！- Yeah！
- 为乔治鼓掌 - 好的
That's my boy right there！That's what I'm…
耶 那是我兄弟
Oh，shit.
可恶
- George。George。The hood。- Hell，no！
- 乔治 乔治 帽子 - 该死不
- Lose the hood。- I know。We're in the 'hood now.
- 别戴了 - 我知道我们是一家人
- No，man。- He's a dead man.
- 不 老兄 - 他完了
You guys feeling me？In the 'hood？
你们还认得我吗 戴着帽子的我
That's it。I'm done.
就这样我尝试过了
Man，you can't give up rap just like that.
兄弟 你不能就这样放弃
Rap- schmap！
饶舌歌最烂
Look，you still got it！See？
可你还是能唱 对吧
Thanks for coming over tonight，Cindy.
谢谢你过来 辛蒂
I guess I'm just going through a rough time.
我想我只是太累了
Brenda，you want to tell me what's really bothering you？
布兰达…要不要告诉我你究竟在烦什么
Well，there's something I need to… I saw a tape.
这个…我有事要说…我看了一卷录影带
I think you should know about it.
我该让你知道这件事
It had these really shocking images，Cindy.
里头的影像很吓人 辛蒂
Brenda，it was Mardi Gras.
布兰达那是忏悔星期二节
I never drank vodka before，and I was out of beads！
我从没喝过伏特加 也没有珠子可给
No，not that tape，Cindy.
不 不是那卷 辛蒂
Well，I guess it's just an urban legend.
我想那只是个传说…
You watch it，
你看那卷带子
and as soon as it's over，your phone rings and a creepy voice says，
只要一结束 你的电话铃会响起
「You're gonna die in seven days.」
一个恐怖的声音会说
And seven days later…
「七天后就是你的死期」
When did you watch it？
过了七天后…你什么时候看的
A week ago.
一星期前
- A week ago tonight。- Brenda…
- 一星期前的今晚 - 布兰达…
Oh，my God！
天啊
Brenda！
布兰达
Brenda！Oh，my God！
天啊
Oh，my God，you bitch！
老天 死三八
Ketchup！
是番茄酱啦
You should have seen the look on your face！
你该看看自己的表情
You got me！
你把我骗倒了
Brenda？Brenda？
布兰达 布兰达
Oh，my God！Brenda！
天啊 布兰达
Brenda！
布兰达
- I can't believe you fell for that fake seizure！- But it seemed so real！
- 没想到你会被骗 - 可是很逼真啊
- It did，didn't it？- And you peed！
- 对吧 很逼真吧 - 而且你还尿出来了
Yeah！I really sold that shit，didn't I？
对呀 我弄得很像真的哦
I just love the look on your face when you are scared.
我就是喜欢看你被吓到的样子
Girl，you are too easy.
你太容易上当了
I got you with the old fake hand！
我用以前那只假手骗你啦
- Girl，you were scared！- Well，I know！
- 小姐你还真害怕 - 对啦对啦
- Come on。I was just kidding。- Well，you've taken it too far，Brenda.
- 拜托 开玩笑而已 - 太过火了 布兰达
I'm gonna go get the rest of the popcorn！
我去拿剩下的爆米花
Cindy？
辛蒂
Forget it。I am not falling for it again.
少来了 我不会再受骗的
Come on.
别闹了
Cindy，the news is on！
辛蒂 是新闻
Another little white girl done fell down a well.
又有一个白人女孩掉进井里
Fifty black people get their ass beat by police today，
今天有50个黑人被警察刑求
but the whole world gotta stop for one little whitey down a hole.
全世界却把焦点放在一个白人女孩身上
Cindy！
辛蒂
The TV's leaking！
电视机在漏水
Cindy？
辛蒂
Cindy，something's wrong here.
辛蒂 这里怪怪的
Cindy，this bitch is messing up my floor！
辛蒂这三八把我地板弄湿了
Cindy，help me！
辛蒂 帮帮我
I'm not listening.
我没听见
Get up，you little ugly bitch.
起来你这小三八
Come on。Let me see what you got.
快点 让我看看你的能耐
What you gonna do？That's all？
你会什么 就这样
I'm whupping her ass，Cindy！
我会打败她的 辛蒂
Yeah！What's up？
怎么样呀
Cindy，please help me！Cindy！
辛蒂 救命辛蒂
Okay，hang on a second。Hello？
好啦 等一下 喂
Father Muldoon here。We're getting along famously.
我是莫顿神父 我们相处得很愉快
Thanks again，Father。Bye- bye.
谢谢你 神父 再见
Brenda？
布兰达
Brenda！
Oh，my God！
天啊
Yes，yes，of course I'll tell her。Thank you.
当然 当然我会告诉她 谢谢
Sue's teacher，Brenda。She's dead.
苏的老师布兰达…她…她死了
- I'd better tell her。- No，no，no。I can do it.
- 我最好跟她说 - 不不不 我可以的
- Sue？- Yes？
- 苏 - 怎么了
- You know your teacher，Miss Brenda？- Yeah？
- 你认识布兰达老师吧 - 认识啊
She's dead！
她死了
Gone forever！Died a horrible，painful death！
永远不回来了 死得好惨
Gone，gone，gone，just like your dog！
死了 死透了 像你的狗狗一样
My dog's dead？
我的狗狗死了
I just ran him over with the car when I drove in！
我回来的时候压到它
Everyone you love around you is dying！
你爱的每个人都死了
Hello，Father.
嗨神父
Don't call me 「Father.」 I haven't been a clergyman since…
别叫我神父 我不当神父很久了自从…
I'm sorry about that night.
那晚的事我很遗憾
If I hadn't fallen asleep while driving for that exact 20 minutes，
如果那20英里路我没打瞌睡
if I hadn't drank that exact whole bottle of Jgermeister，
如果我没有喝光整瓶酒
if I hadn't raped and mutilated that exact mulatto hitchhiker…
如果我没杀了那个搭便车的人
- Sayaman… - …if I hadn't been caught in that
- 沙亚蔓… - 如果当时我没被抓到
exact motel room with those exact two boys…
在那房间跟2个男孩…
Sayaman。I don't see what any of this has to do with Annie.
你说的和安妮都没关系
I'm sorry。Those were other nights.
抱歉 我想到别晚去了
But if it had been that night，
不过如果发生在那一晚
I might have missed her。That terrible night.
或许我不会撞到她 可怕的那一晚…
- It's your wife，Father。She's hurt。- Annie？
- 神父 是您夫人 她受伤了 - 安妮
She was hit by a truck and she's pinned against a tree.
她被卡车撞到 卡在树上动弹不得
I don't understand.
我听不懂
As long as the truck has her pinned，she'll stay alive.
只要不移开卡车她就一息尚存
I still don't get it.
我还是不懂
This is your wife.
这是你太太
She broke her wiener？
她的热狗折断了
Look what happens to the taco.
仔细看这薄饼
Look，I don't understand all this fancy medical lingo。I wanna see Annie.
这么深的譬喻我看不懂 我只想见见安妮
She's split in half.
她被撞成两截了
You mean，like down- the- middle in half？
你是说…从中间折一半了
At the waist.
是从腰部
You mean this is the last time I can talk to the top half？
你是说这是我最后一次跟她的上半身讲话
Yes。The truck is the only thing that is holding her together.
对 是卡车让她暂时黏在一起的
Let's say this is her bottom half.
假设这是她的下半身
Can I squeeze in a few minutes with that？
我可以跟那里温存一下吗
I'm not sure what you mean.
我不懂你的话
- Let me explain。- Tom.
- 让我解释给你听 - 汤姆
Go to her.
去看看她吧
Tom，I'll need a ride home.
汤姆我想搭便车
Hey，baby。How's it going？
宝贝 怎么了
I'm dying，Tom.
我要死了 汤姆
Don't talk like that。The truck barely hit you.
别这么说 卡车差点撞到你
Honey，kiss me one last time.
亲爱的 吻我最后一次吧
Promise me you'll never remarry.
答应我你不会再娶
I promise.
我答应你
And no sex，either.
也不能乱搞
I'm sorry。I didn't catch that.
抱歉我听不懂
- No sex。- Honey，you're not speaking clearly.
- 不能跟人上床 - 亲爱的 你口齿不清了
- Your injuries must be awful。- No sex.
- 你的伤势太严重 - 不能跟人上床
- Cruel fate to shroud my wife's… - No sex.
- 命运之神何其残忍 - 不能跟人上床
- …dying words in mystery。- No sex.
- 让我听不懂吾妻临终之言 - 不能跟人上床
- No sex！- Poor Annie.
- 不能跟人上床 - 可怜的安妮
We hardly knew her。She'll be missed terribly.
我们太不了解她了 我们会很想念她的
- Jesus。- That's right，honey，go into the light.
- 老天爷 - 好的 亲爱的 安息吧
Look！
听着
Just tell George，「Swing away.」
跟乔治说 尽情挥棒
Right。Swing away.
好 尽情挥棒
Sure。That you understand.
这句你又听懂了
Annie？Annie！
安妮 安妮
I'm sorry，dude.
很抱歉老兄
Don't call me dude。I'm not a stoner anymore，not since…
别叫我老兄 我很久没抽大麻了自从…
Goodbye，Tom.
拜了 汤姆
I'm so sorry，Mr。and Mrs。Meeks.
抱歉米克斯先生太太
Brenda was a good friend
布兰达生前是个好朋友
when she was alive.
我可爱的布兰达
My sweet，sweet Brenda。She looks so peaceful.
她看起来很平静
If only God had taken us instead of our daughter.
上帝应该召唤我来代替女儿死的
And knowing your Brenda like I did，I'd say she wishes the same thing.
我了解布兰达 她心中也一定这么想
These just came today.
今天才收到的
Photos from a trip she took.
她旅行时拍的照片
- They're blank。- Turn them around，honey.
- 什么都没有 - 请翻面 亲爱的
Yes，of course.
哦对哦
- Who's this？- That's Ralph.
- 这是谁 - 雷夫
He's right over there.
他就在那里
Cody？
科迪
It's a boy。He's going to be an asshole.
是个男孩 他以后会变成混蛋
Smoke all you want。You're gonna get hit by a bus.
尽量抽吧 反正你会被公车撞死
That's not fooling anyone.
假发骗不了人的
- Cindy。- George.
- 辛蒂 - 乔治
Hey。Sue wanted to pay her respects to her teacher.
苏想向她的老师致意
- You？- Brenda was my bitch.
- 你呢 - 对 布兰达是我好朋友
Of course.
当然
Are you okay？
你还好吧
It's just the open coffin.
是因为棺材还开着
I can't believe they just leave it out here like this.
我真不敢相信他们就这么摆着
- George，it's a wake。- Awake？
- 乔治她醒了 - 醒了
- Brenda！It's a miracle！- No！George，stop！
- 布兰达 奇迹出现了 - 不 乔治 不要
I thought you were dead！
我还以为你死了
Sue，your teacher's alive！
苏 你的老师复活了
- Hello？- What did he say？
- 哈…罗 - 他说什么
I got your back，George！I got your back！
我来罩你 乔治 我来罩你
I'll tell you what！
我告诉你哦…
Mahalik，she's alive！Brenda！
她还活着 布兰达
George，stop！She's dead！
乔治 不要 她已经死了
Brenda！No！We won't lose you again！
不 我们不要再失去你了
Mahalik，help！
没用
Nothing！
没什么
- She's not breathing！- No！
- 她没有呼吸 - 不
Live，damn it！Live！
活过来
Don't！
不要
Live，damn it！Live！
可恶 活过来
Let me open her windpipe！
我让她的气管保持畅通
- Charles！Charles，stop them！- Breathe！
- 天啊 查尔斯 查尔斯 - 呼吸
Someone stop them！What are they doing？
阻止他们 他们在做什么
Get off！
下去
She's alive！She's alive！
她还活着 她还活着
Wake up！Brenda，Brenda，breathe！
醒醒 布兰达 呼吸
Clear！
大家让开
No！
不
I got something！I got something！
我拿到了
- That's it！- George！
- 够了 - 乔治
That's the last time I try to bring anyone back from the dead.
这是我最后一次让人死而复生
George，don't get down on yourself。I know you were only trying to help.
乔治 别怪罪自己 我知道你只是想帮点忙
You're a good，caring person，
你是个好心又体贴的人
which is why I like you.
所以我才喜欢你
Thanks，Cindy，but I don't wanna screw your life up，too.
谢谢你 辛蒂 可我不想要扰乱你的生活
The most caring thing I could do for everyone right now
我走
is to just get out of here.
就是帮大家一个大忙了
George！What about Sue？
乔治 那苏怎么办
Yes。Of course。Once I get Sue，then…
哦对 对哦 只要接到苏我就…
Wait！
等等
I could really use a friend right now.
我现在真的很需要朋友
Brenda's gone，Cody resents me.
布兰达走了 科迪又恨我
And I'm caught up in something I can't even…
我又遇上了奇怪的…
Oh，God，it's so hard！
天啊好难过（双关语 好硬）
Well，you're beautiful and you're pressing up against me.
这个嘛…你这么美 又靠在我身上
Look，Cindy，
听着 辛蒂
I know you'd never consider going out with a guy like me，
我知道你不会跟我这种人约会
but if you're not too busy tomorrow night…
但如果明晚你有空的话…
- Is that a yes？- Yes.
- 那是答应罗 - 对
Cindy，did Brenda ever talk to you about a tape？
辛蒂 布兰达跟你提过录影带的事吗
She did mention something.
她的确提过
Do you mind if I go upstairs and look around？
你介意我上去看看吗
Yes，go。Of course。Go.
当然不会去吧
Cody，I'll be right back，okay？
科迪 我马上回来好吗
You're getting laid tonight。He doesn't know you're a guy.
你今天走运了 他不知道「你」是男人
Oh，shit.
可恶
Hello？
喂
What？Willie Mays？
什么 米丽梅
Who's gay？Hello？
谁是同性恋 喂
…me now？
得…到…吗
What？
什么
- Can you hear me now？- Kind of.
- 听…得…到…吗 - 好像可以
- Can you hear me now？- Yes，perfect.
- 听得到吗 - 清楚了
- Seven days。- Seven days？
- 七天 - 七天
Oh，my God。I'm gonna die next Monday？
天啊 我下星期一就会挂了
Yes。No，wait。Monday。That would be seven business days.
没错 不对 等等 星期一吗 那是工作天的算法
- This is seven days starting now。- So seven days to this very hour？
- 我是说从今天开始算七天 - 现在就开始
My watch broke。How am I gonna know the exact hour？
我的表坏了 我怎么会知道几点开始
Forget hours。This day，seven days from now.
别管几点了 就是今天 从现在开始七天后
But there's a holiday coming up。Do you count the holiday as a day？
可是就快放假了 假日也算在内吗
Well，that depends。What holiday？
这个嘛…要看情形 是什么节日呢
- Martin Luther King Day。- Then no.
- 马丁路德纪念日 - 那不算
Why not？Everybody at work is taking it off.
为什么不算 大家都放假啊
Jesus Christ，lady。I'm giving you seven friggin' days.
我的老天爷 我给你整整七天了
I can come over there now
信不信我现在就过去
and kill the shit out of you if you'd rather have that.
马上取你性命
George，I don't care what you say，man.
不管你怎么说
I'm signing you up for another rap battle.
我要帮你报名另一个比赛
Mahalik，I told you。That part of my life is over.
马哈利 我说过了 我已经不眷恋了
I said the same thing about getting with CJ's sister.
我也曾对CJ的姐姐死心
- But look at me。I'm still hitting that。- He's still hitting it，man！
- 可是你瞧 我还是跟她有一腿 - 你还是跟她有一腿
And she fine as shit！That's my sister！What？
她还是过得好好的 那是我老姐耶 什么
It doesn't matter。I'm done.
这不相干我不玩了
So，what are you gonna do with the rest of your life，dawg？
那你以后想怎么办
I don't know.
我不知道
Yeah，yeah！Come on！
耶 耶 来呀
Maybe my brother was right。Maybe I should just settle down.
或许我哥哥是对的 我应该定下来了
- What's up，then？- Mother…
- 会怎样呢 - 你妈
I got another one，y'all.
又搞到一个了哦
Well，George，man，you can't focus on that shit，man。Let that go.
唷 乔治老弟 不要一直记得旧事 让它过去吧
Hey，you gotta try this shit，George.
想不想试试看 乔治
- Yo，man，you got to take the lid off！- What's wrong with you，man？
- 你得先拿掉盖子 - 你怎么回事啊
- Yes，of course。- Sorry！
- 哦对哦 当然罗 - 抱歉
- Hello？- George，something terrible has happened.
- 喂 - 乔治 可怕的事情发生了
I really need your help.
我需要你的帮忙
- Cindy，are you okay？What's going on？- George！George，you have to help me.
- 辛蒂 你好吗 怎么了 - 乔治 你得帮帮我
I just watched this tape，the same tape that killed Brenda.
我看了那卷录影带 就是杀死布兰达那卷
And then the phone rang，
然后电话就响了
and this voice said that I was gonna die in seven days.
有声音说我七天后会死
Cindy，there's no such thing as a killer videotape.
辛蒂没有杀人录影带这回事
Hell，yeah，there is！
有这回事
In fact，I know somebody who can definitely help you with that.
我认识一个人可以帮你
- You do？Who？- Wait up，man.
- 是吗 谁 - 等等 老兄
I heard Jamal from 90th Street，he watched that tape last week.
我听说90街的杰米尔 他上礼拜看了录影带
- And this morning he woke up dead。- No！
- 今天早上要醒来时就葛屁了 - 不
How in the hell do you wake up dead？
葛屁了怎么醒来
'Cause you're alive when you go to sleep.
我是说他上床前还好好的呗
- Wait。Just tell me who can help me。- So you telling me
- 等等 谁能帮我忙 - 你来告诉我
that you can go to bed dead and wake up alive？
你是说有人可以葛屁着上床又好好的醒来
You can't go to bed dead！Man，that shit would be redundant.
葛屁了何必上床啊 老兄 那叫脱裤子放屁
- Just tell me who。- No，it wouldn't.
- 究竟谁能帮我 - 不可能
'Cause you can go to bed and not be dead，
你可以活着上床
and you can die but not be in a bed.
或是不在床上葛屁
But you are in a bed，man.
可是你已经在床上了
That's how you wake up dead in the first place，fool！
所以才会说「醒来时就葛屁了」
Damn！That's some quantum shit right there，man！
去 真是太深奥了
- That's what I'm talking about。- You should be teaching classes！
- 所以我说嘛 - 你去开一门课算了
- You steady dropping knowledge！- Just tell me who can help me！
- 你太有才了 - 快说谁能帮我
- Damn！- My Aunt ShaNeequa.
- 去 - 真是的夏妮克阿姨可以
Her and her man are into all this weird shit.
她跟她客兄都搞神秘的
They saw the tape before anybody else knew about it.
他们最早看到那卷片子
Matter of fact，you should go see them tonight.
你今晚应该去找他们
- Tonight？Yeah。- Yeah.
- 今晚 - 对
But who will take care of Cody？
那谁要照顾科迪
George，we're gonna have so much fun.
乔治 我们一定会很愉快的
I have some jigsaw puzzles and board games
我有拼图 大富翁…
and baseball cards in my room，and this really cool model airplane.
房间里有棒球卡 还有很酷的模型飞机
- I'm gonna go get it。- Sure.
- 我去拿过来 - 好
Okay，so I made him a snack，
我帮他做了点心
and you can give him some warm milk if he can't go to sleep…
如果他睡不着 你可以冲牛奶给他
Don't worry.
别担心
- Everything's gonna be fine。- Here it is.
- 不会有事的 - 在这里
I'm great with kids。Heads up，Cody.
我跟孩子处得很好 注意了 科迪
And in case of emergencies，
如果有紧急事件…
- I left some numbers… - I'm okay.
- 我留下了一些电话 - 我没事
Sorry。You okay，kiddo？That a boy！
抱歉 你还好吧 小鬼
And I guess that's it.
好孩子
- Okay，I'm off。- Right.
- 好我走了 - 好
You know，it's funny。All a child ever really wants is a family.
你知道吗 真是的 一个小孩最想要的就是…一个家
Yo.
我知道
- Cody really likes you。- He's a good kid.
- 科迪很喜欢你 - 他是个乖小孩
Yeah.
对呀
- Bye。- Bye.
- 再见 - 再见
- Hello？- I know.
- 哈罗 - 我知道
You're Cindy。Be right with you.
你是辛蒂 我马上过来
Aunt ShaNeequa？
夏妮克阿姨吗
Bingo。But you can call me the Oracle。And don't worry about that vase.
答对啦 不过你可以叫我祭师 不必介意花瓶的事
What vase？Sorry，I didn't know.
什么花瓶 抱歉 我不知道
That vase.
就是那个花瓶
Please，sit.
坐吧
It was the chair.
是椅子的关系
Yes，the chair.
对 是椅子
I know why you've come。A great mystery lies ahead of you，
我知道你的来意 你面临了大秘密
but you must not shy away from the challenge.
但你绝不能逃避挑战
Only you can be the one who will…
只有你可以…
- Orpheus？- What，baby？
- 奥菲斯 - 怎么了 亲爱的
Sweetie？
亲爱的
I'm watching the game.
我在看球赛
Do you mind？
可以离开一下吗
The Lakers will win by 12.
湖人队会赢12分
- So can you tell me about… - The tape？
- 那么 你可以谈谈… - 录影带是吗
- Yes。I watched it，and… - The phone rang.
- 对我看了 然后… - 电话响了
- Right。And then this voice said… - That you would die in seven days.
- 对有个声音说… - 你会在七天后死亡
- Okay，that's getting… - Extremely annoying.
- 对 这让我… - 很困扰
- Yeah。- Try being married to her.
- 对 - 跟她结婚很恐怖哦
I catch shit about women I ain't slept with yet.
我还没跟人上床她就发现了
You made a copy of the tape。Let's see it.
你拷贝了一卷带子我们来瞧瞧吧
Yes，okay.
好 好的
ShaNeequa，can you tell me if…
你可以告诉我…
The tape is connected to the crop circles and the aliens？Yes.
录影带和麦田圈有关系吗 有的
But it's up to you to discover how for yourself.
但其中关联要由你来发现
- Look，it's a… - Cigarette？
- 看 这是… - 香烟
I was going to say 「lighthouse.」
我要说的是灯塔
Find that lighthouse。It's your destiny.
找到那座灯塔 那是你的宿命
Wait。What is that？
等等 那是什么
Oh，my God.
天啊
There we go.
好了
Now，baby…
亲爱的…
I knew that was gonna happen.
我知道会发生这事
Come on.
快闪
Hell，no。Get your ass out the TV！
不 你赶快离开电视机前面
What's wrong with you？I'm gonna teach you not to be…
你是怎么回事 让我给你点教训
- Get out that TV！- Baby，no！No！
- 滚出电视机 - 宝贝 不要
- No！Let her go！Let her go！Let her go！- Yeah！
- 让她走吧 - 对
Come on，we gonna get another lawsuit。Come on！
不 拜托 这样我们又会被告的
She spit on me。I'll kill the bitch.
她吐我口水 我要杀了这三八
You won。You won。You won。You won.
你赢了 你赢了 你赢了…
- Upstairs。Upstairs。- Okay。Okay.
- 打上面… - 对对
- Down low。- Okay.
- 打下面 - 好啦
- All right。- Baby，no！
- 好了吗 - 宝贝 不要
- Kill her！Is you crazy？Is you crazy？- Baby！
- 杀了她 你疯了吗 - 宝贝
- What you gonna brush now？- Cool down.
- 看你还梳什么 - 冷静
What you gonna brush now，huh？
看你还梳什么 看你还梳什么
You picked the wrong TV to come out of.
你选错爬出来的电视机了
George？Cody？
乔治 科迪
George？
乔治
- What happened？- I don't know.
- 发生什么事了 - 我不知道
Cody and I were playing a fun game，and then I looked down and…
我们在玩一个很好玩的游戏 然后我往下看 然后…
Yahtzee！
胡了
No！
不
Oh，my God！
我的天啊
- How could you let him watch the tape？- I didn't…
- 你怎么可以让他看 - 我没有呀…
- Hello？- It's me.
- 喂 - 是我啦
- How you doing？- Fine.
- 你好吗 - 还好
Enjoying your last week？I can't wait to see you.
享受最后一个星期吗 好想赶快看到你哦
- Six days now，right？- Yeah.
- 还剩六天对吧 - 对
Well，it was great catching up，but can I speak to Cody？
好 跟你叙旧很愉快可以跟科迪说话吗
Why？He didn't watch the tape.
为什么 他又没看录影带
Yes，he did。Come on，Cindy，I do this for a living.
有 他有 拜托 辛蒂 我是做这一行的耶
Leave us alone！
放过我们
- Hello？- Hello，
- 喂 - 喂
I'm calling from Reader's Digest with a fantastic offer for Cody.
这里是读者文摘 我们对科迪有个优惠方案
No，you're not！You're that evil little girl from the tape！
不 你才不是 你是录影带里那个邪恶女孩
Okay，you got me。How about I just leave a message for him？
好 被你拆穿了 那我留个口信给他好了
Fine.
好吧
Yeah。Okay，how do you spell that？
好 怎么写啊
Right。Okay，got it。Bye- bye.
好 我会了 再见
- I can't believe you let that happen。- I know。I'm sorry，I screwed up…
- 你居然让这种事发生 - 我知道 抱歉我搞砸了
Listen，we can still save him.
听着我们还是能救他的
The answer to the tape，to your crop circles，is at a lighthouse.
录影带的答案 还有麦田圈的答案 一切都在灯塔那里
- You think I'm crazy，don't you？- Of course I do，
- 你不会认为我疯了吧 - 我当然这么认为
but the last thing you need now is a screw- up like me.
不过你现在最不需要的就是我这种逊
- I'm gonna leave for good。- Wait.
- 我要永远地离开 - 等等
Well，what should I tell Cody？
这个…我要怎么跟科迪说
Let him down easy。Tell him I got called away on business.
别让他烦心 就说我必须出差
You'll think of something.
你会想出说词的
Testicular cancer。He won't ask questions.
睾丸癌 这样他就不会乱问
- I knew you'd understand。- George！
- 我就知道你会谅解的 - 乔治…
Just be careful。Something weird is going on at your farm。I know it.
要小心 你家农场有怪事发生 我知道的
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不懂你在说什么
Sometimes a sheep just needs to be pushed through the fence.
有时候羊儿也需要「发泄」一下
- What？- Goodbye，Cindy.
- 你说啥 - 拜拜罗 辛蒂
Sue？
苏
I can't sleep.
我睡不着
Well，it's way past your bedtime.
已经超过你睡觉的时间了
Won't you rock me to sleep in your big，strong arms？
可以用你强壮的臂膀摇摇我吗
There's plenty of room under the covers.
被子里还有很多空间
It's a hot night.
天气好热
You don't need to wear pajamas.
你不用穿睡衣的
Where is my daughter？
我女儿在哪里
Are you mad？I am your daughter.
你疯了是吗 我就是你女儿
No，you're not！
不 你不是
Come here！
过来这里
- What did you do with Sue？- I didn't touch her。I swear.
- 你对苏做了什么 - 我发誓我没碰她
- I don't believe you！- Please！For God's sakes，she's a girl！
- 我不相信你 - 拜托老天做证 她只是个小女孩
You sick…
你这个变态…
Daddy！
爹地
How do you like it，huh？Having fun？
你喜欢吗 感觉如何 好玩吗
Tom，are you…
汤姆 你…
What in the world？
这是什么世界
Look.
看
What is that thing？
那是什么东东
I don't know.
我不知道
Maybe Cindy was right.
或许辛蒂是对的
Please，sir。All I need is five minutes.
拜托先生 我只需要五分钟
And I told you，Campbell，no more paranoid on- air rants
我说过了 辛蒂 我不想听电视台里
about the supernatural.
那些神经又迷信的谣言
I know。This station is about sex，violence and the weather.
我知道 这是个色情电台 也讨论暴力和天气
Yes。That reminds me.
这倒提醒了我
We're gonna need that 「Porn Star Shot Dead in a Hurricane」 story.
我们需要AV女优在飓风中死亡的那则新闻
One hour.
播个一小时吧
Meanwhile，a tornado in Charleston
还有 查尔斯顿的龙卷风袭击海滩
threatens a clothing- optional beach where，just yesterday，
昨天有一对裸体情侣
a naked couple was brutally murdered.
因此罹难
- This just five miles from the spot… - I'm sorry.
- 发生地点距… - 抱歉
…where the last naked couple was brutally murdered.
上一个谋杀案仅差5英里
Turning now to sports.
回到运动新闻
And an evil videotape that kills anyone who watches it in seven days.
有一卷神秘录影带 看过的人会在七天后死亡
It's true。We're all in danger.
是真的 我们都有危险
- There's an alien force out there… - Oh，no.
- 有外星力量在那里 - 不对
…that's trying to prevent you from knowing the truth.
那是要混淆视听罢了
- Campbell，are you insane？- Trust me，it's a horrible fate.
- 坎培尔 你疯了吗 - 相信你的命运
- Carson，I have to do this。- Do you hear me？
- 卡森我必须这么做 - 你听到没
Correction，there really is no danger.
更正 这件事毫无危险性
Actually，I didn't really mean anything I just said.
其实 我只是随便说说
Yes，I did。Every word of it.
对 随便说的
Everyone watching this could be dead in a week.
每个字都不算数 看过的人可能会在一周后死亡
1-3-4-19…
4-6-9…
I been cleaning after this dumb- ass cracker，Giggins，for 10 years.
我为这个笨蛋打扫十年了
But I been waxing his bitch's ass for 12.
我跟他老婆瞎搞了十二年
Know what I'm saying，nigger？
知道我在说啥吗 黑鬼
I ride that ho like your mama rides the bus.
玩骑马打仗
She likes her some chocolate.
她喜欢「巧克力」嘛
Sharpton for President，y'all。I'm outty.
为总统加油 各位 我是李事端
Peace.
要和平哦
An evil videotape that kills people in seven days？
邪恶录影带七天内杀人
Alien forces threatening the world？
外星力量威胁地球
And who in the hell is this Cindy Campbell？
究竟谁是辛蒂.坎培尔
If what she says is true，we're facing an unprecedented crisis.
如果她所言属实 我们就面临空前的危机
- Get me the President。- You are the President.
- 打电话给总统 - 你就是总统
Good。Then I already know about this。Let's order lunch.
很好 那我早就知道这事了 订午餐吧
Sir，I think you need to go on TV
长官 我认为您应该上电视
and convince the people that there is no such thing as a UFO.
告诉大家没有一这回事
Don't spell in front of me，damn it.
别在我面前拼字 讨厌
Aliens，sir。There's no such thing as aliens.
外星人 长官 没有外星人这回事
- That's not quite true。- Sir？
- 这句话不太正确 - 长官
A year ago，a UFO crash- landed in New Mexico.
一年前一架飞碟在新墨西哥州坠毁
- A body may have been recovered。- 「May have been」？
- 可能还找到一具尸体 - 可能
Well，there was a terrible mix- up.
这个嘛…因为都混在一起了
It was Thanksgiving。The body was sent down to the kitchen.
当时是感恩节 尸体被送到厨房
They shoved stuffing up its ass，and we ate it at a state dinner.
他们从屁屁里塞了馅料 我们就当国宴吃掉了
That's the last I saw of it.
那是我最后一次见到它
No，scratch that。There were some sandwiches made the next day.
不 把这记下来 第二天还做了三明治
- Mr。President！Listen to me carefully。- Agent Thompson！
- 总统先生 仔细听我说 - 汤普森
Back away from that window！
离窗户远一点
What？Did I forget to put my pants on again？
什么 我又忘了穿裤子了
No，sir.
不是的 先生
It's just a feeling I've been having since the news about the aliens.
自从听到外星人的消息后我就有个感觉
- Something's not right。- I know what you mean.
- 事情不太对劲 - 我知道你的意思
Like that feeling that something's not right.
就像事情不太对劲的感觉
What is it？
是什么
Some old Tupac，sir.
是首老歌 长官
All Eyez on Me。Hey，this shit is banging.
「月亮代表我的心」 这玩意儿真好听
Thank you，sir。I appreciate it.
谢谢你 我很感谢您
Hello，Cindy.
嗨 辛蒂
I am the Architect。You have many questions.
我是设计者 你有很多问题
I've been watching you for a very long time.
我注意你很久了
So I see.
所以我知道
But what is the connection between the crop circles and the videotape？
麦田圈和录影带究竟有何关联
The answer is simple。You are the eventuality of an anomaly.
答案很简单 你是偶然的必然结果
You are inexorably seeking a sedulant probability.
你在找寻一个奇特的机会
- 「Sedulant」？- Grotesquery？No？
- 诡谲 - 怪异 不是吗
What about 「contingent affirmation」？That's got to mean something.
还是「权宜的确认」 总有个涵义吧
Hey！Hey！You put cameras in my bathroom？
你在我浴室里装针孔
I can't… What is this？
我真是…这是什么
Oh，my God。Well，it was a long winter。I…
天呀 哎呀 冬天很长的
- This is an invasion of… - Sorry.
- 这侵犯了… - 抱歉
I can't help it。It's very lonely in here.
我就是忍不住 这里太寂寞了
Ergo，I haven't been with anyone in a very long time，
很久没有人跟我作伴了
not counting myself，or this chair.
我自己不算 这椅子也不算
I call her… Linda.
我叫她琳达
Could you just cut to the chase？I'm kind of in a rush.
废话少说可以吗 我在赶时间
Why？You can always sleep over if you want.
为什么 只要你愿意就可以住下来
Linda's built for two，and she vibrates.
琳达可负荷两个人 还可以震动哦
Stop it！Just tell me what I need to know！Who is that little girl？
别说了 我只想知道重点 那个小女孩是谁
Okay，okay！
好啦好啦
My wife and I wanted a child，but she couldn't get pregnant.
我老婆和我想要个孩子 但她不能生育
- Neither could I。- So you adopted？
- 我也不能 - 所以你们领养了一个
We loved our daughter，but she was evil.
我们爱这个女孩 但是她很邪恶
Made the horses crazy，killed our puppies，
她令马匹都疯了 杀了我们的小狗狗
hid the remote，really sick shit.
还把遥控器藏起来 真的很病态
My wife took her to the old family farm and drowned her in the well.
我太太把她带到旧家农场 把她丢到井里淹死了
I felt a simple time- out would've been sufficient.
我以为事情就结束了
But Tabitha imprinted her evil on a videotape.
谁知道塔碧莎将邪恶烙印在录影带里
- I never meant for it to get out，but… - But what？
- 我不是故意让它流出去的 可是… - 可是什么
I put it in the wrong box and returned it to Blockbuster，
我不小心放错盒子 还到百视达去了
instead of my copy of Pootie Tang.
还以为是「少林足球」呢
And it's been circulating and killing ever since.
带子一直流传杀人无数
Just like Pootie Tang.
就像「少林足球」一样
- But what does this have to do with aliens？- I don't know.
- 那这跟外星人有什么关系 - 我不知道
Perhaps Tabitha's summoning them to kill us all.
说不定塔碧莎召唤他们来杀光我们
An alien invasion？I have to warn the world.
外星人入侵 我得警告全世界
It's already begun。You're too late.
已经开始了 你已经太迟了
Oh，my God.
老天爷
But not too late to make an old man happy.
不过让个老头子乐乐可永远不嫌迟
What？What？
怎么了 又怎么了
And now，reports of lights in the sky.
现在 关于空中闪光
Glimpses of spacecraft.
幽浮的行踪
Possible alien sightings being reported all over the world.
或是看到外星人的通报 在全球各地出现
Are they aliens？
他们是外星人吗
The first video images are coming in.
第一批画面进来了
Disturbing home video tonight from a ranch outside Sydney，Australia.
来自澳洲雪梨农场令人发指的家庭录影带
Watch very carefully now.
现在请仔细看
There。There it is。Let's see that again.
就在那里 再看一次
Very，very disturbing.
非常非常不清楚
And this just in from So Paulo，Brazil.
这是巴西圣保罗传来的画面
Let's see that again.
我们再看一次
Very，very disturbing.
非常非常不清楚
And this just in from south Texas.
南德州传来的最新画面
Do they pose a threat？Only one thing's for certain.
他们有敌意吗 只有一件事可以确定
We are all going to be killed.
我们都会被杀死
We have to board up the house.
我们要把房子对起来
Are you sure this is necessary，Wilson？
你确定这有必要吗
Having an awards ceremony at a time like this？
在这种时候还举行颁奖典礼
Yes，sir。Everything must appear business as usual.
是的 长官 一切都该如常
The nation，while not yet panicked，is deeply disturbed.
举国上下虽谈不上惊慌失措 但已经严重受到影响
Right。Good，let's see if we can steer that course，
我们来看看是否可以转移大家的焦点
keeping everybody deeply disturbed。We don't want a panic.
我不想引起恐慌
Very few presidents have faced a crisis like this.
很少有总统需要面对这种危机
I wonder what President Ford would've done.
不知道福特会怎么做
Well，if the buck stops here，the buck stops here.
好 闲聊到此结束 到此结束罗
Thank you，all，and welcome to the White House.
感谢并欢迎大家到白宫来
The Mother Teresa Awards recognize those
德蕾莎修女奖表扬
who have overcome the severest handicaps and disadvantages
那些克服残障
to help others in their communities.
而帮助他人的人
The young，the old，black and white.
不论年轻或年老
Our Native- American friends。Hey，how are you？
白人 黑人或是原住民
Hey，how are you？Hey，how are you？Hey，how are you？
你好吗 你好吗 你好吗
Well，it is therefore my honor
好啦这是我的光荣
to present each and every one of you with this symbol of merit.
让我把奖项颁发给大家
The room is secure，Mr。President.
这个房间是安全的 总统先生
- Or is it？- Sir？
- 或许吧 - 长官
I've been thinking，Thompson.
我还在想
What if the aliens could take over human bodies？
如果外星人占据人类身体呢
They'd look just like us，or almost.
他们看起来就像我们一样 几乎一样
I never thought of that，sir.
我从没这么想过
We should be on alert for anything suspicious.
我们要保持警觉
- They could be anywhere，even… - Right here.
- 他们可能出现在任何地方 甚至… - 就在这里
My God。We'd never see the attack coming.
天啊 我们从没经压过外星人入侵
- It's frightening，sir！- Don't panic.
- 好可怕哦 长官 - 别惊慌
We'll just move slowly toward the exit.
我们慢慢地朝出口移动
At last we meet，Mr。President.
终于见到你了 总统先生
It's happening。I knew it！You'll never take me alive！
发生事情了 我就知道 你不可能活捉我的
She's scrambling my brain！
她在干搅我的脑
I'll get her！
我抓到她了
No，you don't！Not on my watch！
不 你不会得逞的 至少在我面前不可能
Good work，sir！
干得好 长官
Good God！The small ones have metal teeth！
天老爷啊 小只的有钢牙
Jerry's Kids，my ass！
杰瑞的小孩 放屁
Mr。President！Mr。President，have you gone completely insane？
总统先生 总统先生 你疯了吗
Like a fox.
像狐狸一样
We gotta talk to the one person who saw this coming，Cindy Campbell.
我得和知道内情的人谈谈 辛蒂.坎培尔
She knows how to defeat the aliens，these filthy，rotten scum！
她知道怎样击退外星人 这些无孔不入的人渣
You hideous creature！Get off my planet！
滚令人做呕的东西 滚出我的星球
No！
他不是有意的
- Mr。President，is everything all right？- The exits are all blocked.
- 总统先生一切都还好吗 - 出口全被堵住了
I'll find one，sir.
我会找到出口的
Everybody，clear！
大家让开
This way，sir！God，this is exciting！
走这里 长官 天啊 好刺激
You're excited？You should feel my nipples.
你很兴奋 你应该摸摸我的乳头
Cody？Cody？
科迪 科迪
Cody，where are you？Honey？
科迪 你在哪里 亲爱的
After today's incident in the East Room，
经过今天在东厢的意外后
the White House is now advising all citizens
白宫建议大家钉好门窗
to board up their homes and prepare for an alien invasion.
准备迎战外星人入侵
Oh，no.
不
And now，a News 8 exclusive，
现在请看第八频道的独家报道
the killer videotape you've been hearing about.
传说中的杀人录影带
- No… - We're the only station that has it，
- 不 - 我们独家取得
and we're showing it all night。Very exciting。Let's roll it again.
今晚为您播映 好刺激哦 再重播一次
There。Nobody's getting through that sucker.
好啦 没有人进得来了
That's great，George，but we have to get down to the cellar.
很好 乔治 不过我们得到地窖去了
- George。- Cindy.
- 乔治 - 辛蒂
There's no time。Get down to the cellar.
没时间了 下去地窖
- Cody！Thank God！- Aunt Cindy！
- 科迪 老天 - 辛蒂
- I've been worried sick about you。- He just showed up about an hour ago.
- 我担心死你了 - 他大约一小时前出现
- I tried to call。- No，he didn't.
- 我试着打电话的 - 不 他没有
- Okay，but I was gonna。- No，he wasn't.
- 好吧我本来要打的 - 不 他没有
Look，Cody，the point is you can't just run away like that.
科迪重点是你不该那样跑走
I wanted to be with George.
我想跟乔治在一起
Honey，I know you want a dad，but…
亲爱的 我知道你想要个父亲 不过…
Trust me，Cody，I'm not good at anything。Why would I be good at that？
相信我科迪 我什么都不在行 怎么能做个父亲
Uncle George！
乔治叔叔
It's gonna be okay，Cody.
不会有事的 科迪
I'm going to die，aren't I？
我会死对不对
Cody，did I ever tell you what your mom said about you the day you were born？
科迪 我跟你说过 你母亲在你出生时说的话吗
No.
没有
I was in the delivery room with her。She was having a hard time.
我一直陪着她 她痛了很久
Then you began to come out of her.
然后你漏出来了
And your mom screamed and screamed in pain.
你妈妈痛苦地大叫
She yelled，「Just kill me。Bludgeon me with a bedpan.
她叫着说 把我杀了吧 用便盆把我打死吧
「Whatever you do，put me out of this pain.」
随你怎么做 别让我再痛了
She was gushing torrents of blood.
她在血渍中不停破口大骂
I have this all on tape if you wanna see it someday.
我拍了下来 想看的话改天你可以看
Well，finally you came out.
终于你生下来了
Your mom cut your umbilical cord herself.
你妈自己把脐带剪断
Well，on the second try.
没错 还试了两次
The first time，she snipped your penis in half.
第一次把你的小鸡鸡剪成两段
After all，she was drunk。Actually，drugged.
毕竟她喝醉了 其实是嗑了药
We'd been out the night before，celebrating Saint Patrick's Day，
我们前一天晚上出去欢度圣派翠克节
and she thought，「Hey，I never tasted crystal meth.」
她想 「我没试过安非他命」
So she did just a little.
所以她吸了点
- My penis？- Yes.
- 我的小鸡鸡 - 对
They sewed it on upside- down.
他们缝反了
- So that's why I pee up？- Yes。We'll get it fixed，honey.
- 所以我尿尿都朝上 - 对 以后再来想办法
It's on my list of things。Right after we get TiVo.
我把这件事记下来了 就记在「装第四台」下面
Anyway，there you were.
总之你生出来了
And your mom turned to me，and she said 「Hey，you want him？Take him.」
你妈转向我说 「你想要这家伙吗？带走吧」
Then she died。And I took you。Do you know why？
然后她就死了 于是我带走了你 你知道为什么吗
I had just lost my cat in a fire，and I needed something to pet and feed.
我在一场大火里失去了猫咪 我需要有东西摸摸喂喂的
And I miss that cat，Cody.
我想念那只猫 科迪
But I love you，and nothing's ever gonna change that，
可是我爱你 没有什么可以改变这一点
not even the very painful death we're about to experience.
即使是我们即将要面对的死亡
George！George.
乔治
- Are they gone？- I don't hear anything.
- 它们走了吗 - 都没有声音了
- Don't worry，Sue。It'll be all right。- It was Uncle George.
- 别担心 苏 没事的 - 是乔治叔叔
Well，it's scary.
唉呀好可怕
Good work，Sue.
很好 苏
I don't know what stupid，idiotic thing made these lights go off.
不知道是什么笨东西让灯熄了
All right，there's some spare fuses in the crawlspace.
有一些多余的保险丝
If I can get to them，I can get these lights back on.
如果可以拿过来 就可以让灯亮起来
Quick，George，grab that railroad tie.
快啊 乔治 拿那个铁轨木条
Jam it against the door.
我来堵住门
My balls！
我的蛋蛋
Not those！Jesus！
不是这些啦 天啊
No！
不用了
Uncle George！I'm scared！
乔治叔叔我很害怕
Sweetie，come here。It's okay.
亲爱的 过来这里 没事的
There's something on the other side of the door.
门的另一头有东西耶
I can't see anything.
我看不到
Oh，my God.
我的天
Can you see them？What are they doing？
你看得到吗 它们在干嘛
They're horrible。They're grayish with big black eyes.
它们好可怕 它们灰灰的 有着大大的黑眼睛
Their teeth are grotesque.
它们的牙齿好丑
- I think they're giggling。- What？
- 它们好像在笑 - 什么
Oh，no.
不
Oh，no，I think…
不好 我想…
I think they wanna eat me.
他们好像要…
- Help！- Cody！Oh，my God！
- 救命 - 科迪
George。Swing away，George.
乔治 尽情挥棒 乔治
- I'm coming，Cody。I'll save you。- Aunt Cindy，help！
- 我来了 科迪 我会救你的 - 辛蒂 救我
Die！
去死吧
Die！You damn aliens，let him go！
去死吧 该死的外星人 放了他
You're not getting in here！
你们进不来的
- What else you got？Bring it！- George…
- 你还有什么 - 乔治
There！Had enough？
使出来啊 受够了吧
Forget it，Cody。Thank me later.
没关系 科迪 以后再谢我吧
Cody。Thank God。Come on.
科迪 谢谢上帝 来吧
- Daddy！Daddy！- Sue！
- 爹地 爹地 - 苏
Mahalik，what are you doing here？
马哈利 你在这里做啥
Hey，man，I told you the 'hood's always got your back.
我说过我永远罩你的
Thank God。There's two of them at the door.
感谢主 门那里有两个
- What？- They're gone.
- 什么 - 它们走了
Good。They couldn't get in。I hear they can't open doors.
好 他们进不来的 我听到它们不能开门
They mastered space flight，but they can't get through a wooden door？
它们可以在太空中飞行 却不能穿过一扇木门
Look，the cellar's the safest place.
地窖是最安全的地方
I say all the women and children stay here.
要我说 所有女人和小孩都在这里
All right，and the men，we go outside and fight.
抱歉 男人我们出去迎战
Right。And what's the cut- off age for children？
对 几岁以下才算小孩
Come on，come on.
走吧
Follow me.
跟我走
I'm sorry。I thought I was hitting the brake.
很抱歉 我以为我踩了刹车
Now，we don't have to go through insurance，do we？
那我们就不必透过保险公司了吧
Mr。President，what are you doing here？
总统先生 你在这里做什么
I'm looking for Cindy Campbell.
我找辛蒂坎培尔
She may hold the key to defeating the aliens.
她可能知道击退外星人的方法
Good。The Air Force is here with those new round planes.
好耶 空军来了 开着新型圆式飞机呢
We don't have round planes，sir.
我们没有圆式飞机 长官
Oh，my God.
我的老天爷
Wait。Do you hear that？
等等 你听到了吗
- Yo，what's up，George？- CJ！
- 唷 什么事呀 乔治 - CJ
I told you，the 'hood always got your back.
我说过了我会永远罩你的
And I got the boys with me。Get out the car，man.
我还把兄弟都找来了 大家下车吧
- Yo，who we gonna shoot？- Y'all ready to go step？
- 唷 要射谁来着 - 准备好开战了吗
Well，let's go do this，'cause I'm hyped right now，B！
好 大家上吧 因为我现在很骇
- I'm real hyped！- You stepped on my shoe，bitch！
- 真的很骇 - 你踩到我了 三八
Call me another bitch again，and I'll park your truck dead in your ass.
你再叫我三八 我就把卡车停到你屁眼里
- Calm down，man。- Damn，homey！
- 冷静下来嘛 - 可恶
- In the cornfield。- They're coming！
- 就像在家似的 - 它们来了
Hey，look，don't even worry about that.
别担心
Me and my boys here，we gonna go ahead and take care of this.
我和男士们会解决的
Hey，yo，come on，let's start it！
来 我们开始吧…
If I was you，son，I'd bust this shit right now.
如果我是你 我会马上轰掉这家伙
- Your mama！- I got your number，too，homey.
- 你娘可好吗 - 我有你家电话
Hey！We over here，y'all！
我们过来罗
He ain't gonna bust nothing。I got nuts bigger than him，ya heard？
我们不会轰掉任何东西 我的蛋蛋比他还大 听到没
Percival，you country- ass，maple- syrup nigger.
你的那个很短吧黑仔
Y'all want some biscuits？You want some biscuits？
想吃子弹吗
Get down！Get down！
趴下
I can't believe what I just saw.
我不敢相信看到什么
These men died for their country。Send flowers to their bitches and hos.
这些人为国捐躯 送花给他们的老婆和马子吧
I can't break free！
我无法脱身
Think！They must have some kind of weakness.
它们一定有弱点的
I found it！
我找到了
Without their heads，they're powerless！
只要没有了头 它们就失去了力量
Please，no。We mean you no harm.
拜托 不要 我们没有恶意
We traveled to your planet to find an evil little girl.
我们到这里来找寻一名邪恶的女孩
We must destroy her before seven days.
我们要在七天内摧毁她
You mean you watched the videotape？
你们也看了录影带
Our satellite picked up what we thought was Pootie Tang.
我们以为那是「少林足球」就在卫星上播出了
That was a week ago.
那是一星期前的事了
And now our entire race will die unless the girl is destroyed.
我们整个星球都会灭亡了除非杀了那女孩
- See？They are peaceful。- Well，if they're so peaceful，man，
- 你看吧 它们很平和的 - 如果它们爱好和平
why were they choking us a few minutes ago？
那刚才干嘛想让我们窒息
That's how we say hello.
那是我们打招呼的方式
Hello！Nice to see you.
哈罗 很高兴认识你
- Hello，hello。- Hello，hello.
- 哈罗 - 哈罗
Well，how do you guys say goodbye？
那你们怎么说再见
I had to ask.
我得问一声啊
If you think that's strange，you should see how we pee.
如果你们觉得奇怪 那你应该看我们怎么撒尿
So we're not so different after all.
所以我们差别并不大
There's something about this place。It's like I've seen it before.
这里怪怪的 好像我以前来过似的
Oh，my God.
天啊
This used to be their farm。She died right here.
这就是旧家农庄 她就死在这里
There's something down there.
这下面有东西
Push back。Follow through.
推回去 跟我做
- Follow through。- Yeah。You got it.
- 跟着做 - 对 你会了
Just look at this。Human beings and aliens working together.
看看这一幕 人类和外星人同心协力
We're all just one big galactic family.
我们都属于银河一族
Family。That's just what I've been running away from.
家族…那是我尽力逃避的东西
Well，that's because you're an idiot.
因为你是笨蛋啊
This is it.
就是这里
My wife took her to the old family farm and drowned her in the well.
我太太带她到旧家农壮 把她丢到井里淹死
The little girl。She's frightened of the well.
这小女孩很怕这口井
Cindy！
辛蒂
Time to go back down the well，bitch.
该回到井底了 三八
- Cindy！- No。Don't hurt him！
- 辛蒂 - 不要 不要伤害他
Cindy，you have to come outside。The aliens aren't invading…
辛蒂 快出来 外星人没有敌意
Don't worry，Cody。I'll save you.
别担心 科迪 我会救你的
Wait！Wait。Don't do this.
等等 别这么做
You don't have to be evil.
你不必使坏的
I know what happened to you，Tabitha.
我知道你发生了什么事
I know what your mom did。That was wrong.
我知道你妈妈做的事 那是不对的
You were just a little girl。And you're still that little girl，
你只是个小女孩 你还是那个小女孩
just a lot more corpsy and with really bad teeth.
只不过像个僵尸 牙齿丑了些
But maybe all you need is a mother.
或许你需要一个母亲
And a father.
和父亲
- We could be… - A family.
- 我们可以组成… - 一个家庭
Thank you all.
谢谢你们
Your love has broken the curse and freed my soul.
你们的爱破解了诅咒解放了我的灵魂
- I'll never have to kill again。- Really？
- 我再也不杀人了 - 真的
Nah！I'm just screwing with you！
不是 只是唬唬你们罢了
I just want to tell you both good luck。We're all counting on you.
我只是想祝你们好运 大家都靠你们了
Now it's over.
一切都结束了
No，no，it's okay。He's our friend.
不 没关系的 它是我们的朋友
Thank you for saving our species。Now we must return to our home planet.
谢谢你拯救我们的族人 我们必须回去了
Goodbye，then.
那就再见了
Goodbye.
再见
Hey，congratulations，George！
恭喜了 乔治
You know the 'hood always got your back.
我们永远会罩你的
Yeah，yeah！Come on！
是啊 是啊 请进
- Bye！- Thank you.
- 再见 - 谢谢
George，I'm so happy。Finally we're a family.
乔治 我好高兴 我们终于是一家人了
Yeah。You，me，and…
对你和我…
- Damn！- Damn！
- 可恶 - 可恶
Cindy！George！Wait！
辛蒂 乔治 等一下